

DAVID **BJÖRKBERG**

PROGRAMMER

About me

I am a programmer with two shipped games and four years of experience working on both single-player and multiplayer open-world games using Unreal Engine, focusing on gameplay, networking and optimization.

Contact



Skövde, Sweden



david.bjorkberg1@gmail.com



davidbjorkberg.github.io

Work Experience

Spellscaper

Feb 2022- Dec 2024

Lead Unreal Engine Programmer

- Worked on an open-world multiplayer game from concept to launch.
- Assisted junior programmers and technical designers.
- Worked closely with game designer to implement and iterate on new systems / gameplay features

Piktiv

Feb 2021 - Feb 2022

System Developer (Unreal Engine)

- Implemented gameplay/systems in C++ and Blueprint
- Profiled and optimized in Unreal
- Worked on a game that is now published on Android and iOS

Attractive Interactive Feb 2020 - Apr 2020

Programming Intern (Unity)

- Developed prototypes that feel good to play
- Worked with game designer to identify how to improve the prototype
- Ended early because of COVID-19

Education

Bachelor of Science (B.S) Digital Game Development

2017-2020

Blekinge Tekniska Högskola

Game Programming

2014-2017

LBS Kreativa Gymnasium